justclicktravels.com 2012-08-27

# Flights, Book Lowest price Flights, Cheap Domestic and International Flights, Hotel Reservations, book exclusive resorts.

Privacy Policy

**What personal information does Just Click Travels gather from me and how is this information used?**

When browsing our site, you are not required to provide any personal information unless and until you choose to make a purchase or sign up for one of our e-mail newsletters or other services as described above. A valid credit card is required to make a purchase on our site.

**Making a Booking?**

In order to purchase travel and related services through our site, you must provide us with certain personal information such as your name, your credit card number and expiration date, your telephone number, your e-mail address and the name or names of the person(s) traveling (if not you). We require this information so that we can process, fulfill and confirm your reservations and transactions and keep you informed of each transaction's status.

**With whom (if anyone) will my personal information be shared?**

When you reserve or purchase travel services through Just Click Travels, we provide to the travel agency or other involved third party only that portion of your personal information that is needed for the successful fulfillment of your travel arrangements.

**What safeguards are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of your information?**

All personal information you provide to Just Click Travels is transmitted using SSL (Secure Socket Layer) encryption. SSL is a proven coding system that lets your browser automatically encrypt, or scramble, data before you send it to us. In addition, when you make travel purchases on Just Click Travels, you are protected.

**What other information should I know about my privacy?**

Just Click Travels contains links to other web sites. Please note that when you click on one of these links, you are entering another web site for which Just Click Travels has no responsibility. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of all such sites as their policies may be materially different from this Privacy Policy. Of course, you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords and credit card numbers. In addition to the circumstances described above, Just Click Travels may disclose member information if required to do so by law, court order, as requested by other government or law enforcement authority.

Thank you for Choosing JustClickTravels.com.
